astrolis.com 2019-06-10

# Privacy Policy

This policy explains what kind of personal information we collect when you use our services. We take your privacy extremely seriously and will never sell lists or email addresses. 

### How Astrolis Collects Information

_Contact Form_  
When you consult with our customer service team, send us an email or communicating with us in any way, you are voluntarily giving us information that we collect to help serve you better. That information may include your name, email address, IP address and software versions for your internet browser, Astrolis mobile application or operating system. By giving us this information, you consent to this information being collected, used, disclosed, transferred and stored by us. 

_Cookies_  
This website may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For session ID cookies, once you close your browser or log out, the cookie terminates and is erased. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your computer's hard drive for an extended period of time. Your browser's help file contains information and instructions for removing persistent cookies. Session ID cookies may be used to track user preferences while the user is visiting the website. They also help to minimize load times and save on server processing. Cookies used on the Astrolis website do not contain personally identifiable information. 

_Log Files_  
Like most standard websites, this website uses log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. However, none of the information stored in the log files, including but not limited to IP addresses, is linked to personally identifiable information. 

_Email Subscription_  
We collect basic information from you when you register for an email subscription, such as email address, astrological sign, timezone and birthday. 

_Information from use of mobile apps_  
When you use our mobile apps, we may collect certain information in addition to information described elsewhere in this Policy. For example, we may collect information about the type of device and operating system you use. We may ask you if you want to receive push notifications about activity in your account. If you have opted in to these notifications and no longer want to receive them, you may turn them off through your operating system or unsubscribe from within the app. We do not ask for, access or track any location-based information from your mobile device at any time while downloading or using our mobile apps or services. We may collect information about how often you use the application and other performance data. 

### How this information is used

Astrolis may use the personally identifiable information collected to contact customers regarding products and services offered by Astrolis, to the extent the customer has agreed to it. Astrolis may also use this information for research purposes regarding the effectiveness of website services, marketing, advertising and sales efforts. Astrolis will not in any way share this information with a third party either for free or by selling it. 

_3rd Party Advertising_  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

_Service Announcements_  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement, if, for instance, a service is temporarily suspended for maintenance. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

### How this information is disclosed

_As Required by Law and Similar Disclosures_  
We may disclose information about you: (i) if we are required to do so by law, regulation, or legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; (ii) in response to requests by government agencies, such as law enforcement authorities; (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect against or respond to physical, financial or other harm, injury, or loss to property; or (iv) in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual unlawful activity. 

_Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers_  
We may disclose your Personal Information to a potential or actual acquirer, successor, or assignee as part of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including in bankruptcy or similar proceedings). 

### Maintenance of Information

The information provided to Astrolis is saved indefinitely and may be stored on one or more databases directly or indirectly maintained by Astrolis. Astrolis employs industry standard security measures to protect the confidentiality of the information. Although Astrolis cannot guarantee that any loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur; every effort is made to prevent such occurrences. 

_Security_  
If a security breach causes an unauthorized intrusion into our system that materially affects you, then Astrolis will notify you as soon as possible and later report the action we took in response. 

_Accuracy and Retention of Data_  
We do our best to keep your data accurate and up to date, to the extent that you provide us with the information we need to do so. If your data changes (for example, if you have a new email address), then you are responsible for notifying us of those changes. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as long as needed to provide you with our Services. We may also retain and use your information in order to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, prevent abuse, and enforce our Agreements. 

_Data Retention_  
We will give you access to any personal information we hold about you within 30 days of any request for that information. Unless it is prohibited by law, we will remove any personal information about you from our servers at your request. There is no charge for an individual to access or update their personal information. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about your personal information or this policy, or if you would like to make a complaint about how Astrolis processes your personal data, please contact Astrolis by email at [privacy@astrolis.com](mailto:privacy@astrolis.com)
